Email

metebezgin@gmail.com

Address

Şirintepe Mahallesi Aşiyan Sokak No : 2

Phone

+905347687697

Date of birth

09-11-1997

Nationality

Turkish

Link

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mete-bezgin/

Skills

Teamwork

Problem-Solving

Customer service

ExpressJS

JavaScript

ReactJS

Django

Flask

Python

NodeJS

Amazon Web Services

RESTful API

Languages

Turkish

Native

English

Advanced

Spanish

Elementary

Mete Bezgin

Web Developer

3 years experienced programmer with solid understanding of object-oriented programming and creating RESTful APIs to connect to backend services, desire the position of Web Developer, to apply technical skills in designing and building responsive web applications. Coming with user-oriented focus, and a solid understanding of ES8 / ES2017, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, React, AWS, TypeScript, Python, MongoDB, Node.js and Docker.

Experience

Middle-Level Full Stack Developer

Truely Portugal (remote from Istanbul)

https://truely.com

April 2020 - May 2022

- Developed fully responsive web pages for optimal user UX and offered debugging services to clients
- · Collaborated with four other engineers to launch a new business web site
- · Created several interfaces using React.js for 200+ internal users daily
- · Built 20+ scrapers running on AWS Lambda as cron jobs

Middle-Level Full Stack Developer

Geonode Portugal (remote from Istanbul)

https://geonode.com

October 2021 - May 2022

- Developed fully responsive web pages for the end-user with the given feedback from UX tests and handled bugs occured during that
- Collaborated with two other developers for backend and one developer for frontend
- · Created custom UI kit using Tailwind CSS and Storybook for admin dashboard
- · Handled pipelines of HubSpot CRM for our payment modules

Middle-Level Full Stack Developer

Upwork Istanbul (remote)

May 2019 - Present

- · Listened my client's needs and acted accordingly
- Created several automation scripts for clients' businesses

Education

Mechanical Engineering

Istanbul Technical University *Istanbul* 2016-2020

Dropout with 110 completed credits out of 155

Software Engineering

Bahcesehir University

Istanbul 2021-Present